Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection AD.MC.002
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971 (Box 1-7)
  - Wedding Portrait Series, 1402
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A seated bride, with her feet on a cushion, holding a bouquet, groom standing behind her wearing tarbouche. 41.0 x 27.9 cm, Undated; cuid1229 (Box 7, Folder 1, Oversize unknown container)
      Men; Women; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Weddings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Weddings; Fez/Tarboush; Weddings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Painted Backdrops; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Jewelry; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride with an ostrich feather fan in her lap and a groom holding white gloves. 38.5 x 29.0 cm, 7 September 1941; cuid1230 (Box 7, Folder 2, Oversize unknown container)
      Gloves; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Women; Men; Women; Weddings; Hand Fans; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride with a tiara and a large bouquet, groom is holding white gloves and wearing a tarbouche. 39.8 x 28.8 cm, Undated; cuid1231 (Box 7, Folder 2, Oversize unknown container)
      Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Egypt; Gloves; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Women; Weddings; Group Portraits; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Tuxedos; Arabic Writing; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom holding hands, the bride wears a three-quarter length dress. 39.2 x 29.0 cm, Undated; cuid1232 (Box 7, Folder 2, Oversize unknown container)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Cairo, Egypt; Weddings; Men; Women; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride sitting in a chair with her hands on her lap, the groom is standing next to her wearing a tarbouche. 36.5 x 30.5 cm, Undated; cuid1233 (Box 7, Folder 2, Oversize unknown container)
      Jewelry; Weddings; Fez/Tarboush; Gloves; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Asyut, Egypt; Women; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Furnishings; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride wearing a dress with tassels, and a groom standing with his arms behind his back. 22.7 x 16.8 cm, Undated; cuid1234 (Box 7, Folder 2, Oversize unknown container)
      Furnishings; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Weddings; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Women; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Painted Backdrops; Group Portraits; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride holding an ostrich feather fan, standing next to a man in a morning coat (same pair as ref1264). 32.7 x 23.0 cm, Undated; cuid1235 (Box 7, Folder 3, Oversize unknown container)
      Weddings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Hand Fans; Cairo, Egypt; Facial Hair; Painted Backdrops; Gloves; Jewelry; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Tuxedos
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride sitting in a chair, holding an ostrich feather fan, the groom stands beside her holding gloves (linked ref1263). 32.7 x 23.0 cm, Undated; cuid1236 (Box 7, Folder 3, Oversize unknown container)
      Weddings; Hand Fans; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Painted Backdrops; Women; Gloves; Cairo, Egypt; Men; Jewelry; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Furnishings; Tuxedos
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A man in military uniform and a bride standing on a carpet. 14.5 x 9.3 cm, Undated; cuid1237 (Box 7, Folder 3, Oversize unknown container)
      Women; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Weddings; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Men; Group Portraits; Medals/Insignia; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom in a horse drawn carriage (negative in collections) 12.3 x 18.1 cm., Undated; cuid1238 (Box 7, Folder 3, Oversize unknown container)
      Carriages/Coaches; Women; Horses; Men; Weddings; Egypt; Animals; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Negative Images; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Weddings; Group Portraits; Children; Head Covers/Veils
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride sitting in a high-backed chair, groom is leaning on a tall table, wearing a tarbouche. 41.0 x 29.3 cm, Undated; cuid1239 (Box 7, Folder 3, Oversize unknown container)
      Men; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Weddings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Tanta/Tantah, Egypt; Fez/Tarboush; Women; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom standing in front of a table with a glass vase on it. 28.5 x 19.5 cm, Undated; cuid1240 (Box 7, Folder 4, Oversize unknown container)
      Men; Weddings; Women; Gloves; Photographic Prints; Bow Ties; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Egypt; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom sitting together, the bride holds a bouquet. 35.5 x 25.5 cm, Undated; cuid1241 (Box 7, Folder 4, Oversize unknown container)
      Furnishings; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Cairo, Egypt; Women; Weddings; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Painted Backdrops; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom holding white gloves. 22.5 x 25.8 cm, Undated; cuid1242 (Box 7, Folder 4, Oversize unknown container)
      Cairo, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Weddings; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Gloves; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Gloves; Painted Backdrops; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom posing in front of a painted backdrop of the moon. 27.3 x 18.8 cm, Undated; cuid1243 (Box 7, Folder 4, Oversize unknown container)
      Weddings; Women; Fez/Tarboush; Photographic Prints; Weddings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Cairo, Egypt; Weddings; Men; Group Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Head Covers/Veils; Painted Backdrops; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Jewelry; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom, the bride is wearing a short dress with lace detailing. 19.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; cuid1244 (Box 7, Folder 4, Oversize unknown container)
      Egypt; Men; Women; Weddings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A seated bride and groom, the bride wears a beaded brocade dress. 39.0 x 28.7 cm, Undated; cuid1245 (Box 7, Folder 5, Oversize unknown container)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Studio Photography; Cairo, Egypt; Weddings; Men; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride seated holding an ostrich feather fan, the groom stands behind her. 34.7 x 25.8 cm, 30-10-1920; cuid1246 (Box 7, Folder 5, Oversize unknown container)
      Weddings; Photographic Prints; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Men; Weddings; Arabic Writing; Weddings; Hand Fans; Jewelry; Carpets/Rugs
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom seated in ornate chairs surrounded by flowers. 16.5 x 22.3 cm, Undated; cuid1247 (Box 7, Folder 5, Oversize unknown container)
      Bow Ties; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Fez/Tarboush; Men; Egypt; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Weddings; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Tuxedos; Jewelry; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride with a long veil seated in a chair with the groom standing behind her holding white gloves, with a painted backdrop in the background. 24.0 x 18.0 cm, Undated; cuid1248 (Box 7, Folder 5, Oversize unknown container)
      Weddings; Men; Gloves; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Egypt; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Carpets/Rugs
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride in a lace dress with a long veil, holding flowers, with a man in a white suit jacket. 24.4 x 17.1 cm, 6 May 1953; cuid1249 (Box 7, Folder 6, Oversize unknown container)
      Weddings; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Studio Photography; Cairo, Egypt; Women; Group Portraits; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride in a long dress with a veil, the groom is wearing a dark suit and glasses. 24.5 x 17.1 cm, 1959; cuid1250 (Box 7, Folder 6, Oversize unknown container)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Weddings; Studio Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Cairo, Egypt; Women; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Jewelry; Carpets/Rugs
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A groom in a white jacket, with the bride seated in a lace dress and long veil. Arabic text on reverse: "Souvenir from Mr Lotfi". 22.2 x 15.8 cm, 11 (?) 1952; cuid1251 (Box 7, Folder 6, Oversize unknown container)
      Weddings; Women; Signatures; Photographic Prints; Bow Ties; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Men; Weddings; Weddings; Egypt; Facial Hair; Tuxedos; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride wearing a tiara, with a groom in a white jacket. 31.8 x 22.8 cm, 17 August 1950; cuid1252 (Box 7, Folder 6, Oversize unknown container)
      Jewelry; Weddings; Alexandria, Egypt; Bow Ties; Men; Women; Weddings; Weddings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A portrait of a man and woman posing outside in a garden, the woman wears a detailed beaded dress. 30.7 x 24.9 cm, Undated; cuid1253 (Box 7, Folder 6, Oversize unknown container)
      Egypt; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gardens; Fez/Tarboush; Weddings; Jewelry; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A seated bride and groom, looking off camera. 33.6 x 24.5 cm, Undated; cuid1254 (Box 7, Folder 7, Oversize unknown container)
      Painted Backdrops; Gloves; Weddings; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Women; Cairo, Egypt; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Carpets/Rugs
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A groom with white gloves standing beside a bride with a bouquet. 34.2 x 28.8 cm, 134 Hijri; cuid1255 (Box 7, Folder 7, Oversize unknown container)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gloves; Weddings; Studio Photography; Women; Cairo, Egypt; Weddings; Weddings; Men; Photographic Prints; Jewelry
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom posing on some steps with their bridesmaids and groomsmen. 24.3 x 36.8 cm, Undated; cuid1256 (Box 7, Folder 7, Oversize unknown container)
      Weapons; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Swords/Knives; Egypt; Women; Weddings; Facial Hair; Tuxedos; Hats
    - Wedding Portrait Series - A bride and groom, the groom wears glasses and hold a pair of gloves. 38.2 x 26.4 cm, Undated; cuid1257 (Box 7, Folder 7, Oversize unknown container)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Weddings; Women; Egypt; Men; Gloves; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - France Series, 1404
    - France Series 1/10 - A building with a large terrace, with two people walking up the stairs. 6.5 x 9.1 cm, Undated; cuid538 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Photographic Prints; Women; Men; Architecture; Buildings; France; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - France Series 2/10 - A street with some buildings in the background. 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid539 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      France; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Street Lamps
    - France Series 3/10 - An ornate awning and some stairs in a park (linked ref572). 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid540 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Parks; France; Architecture; Men; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Canes/Walking Sticks; Hats
    - France Series 4/10 - Women in maid uniforms cleaning a railing while men look on. 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid541 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Photographic Prints; Architecture; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Buildings; France; Restaurants/bars; Group Portraits
    - France Series 5/10 - People sitting under an ornate awning/portico (linked ref573) 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid542 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women; Men; France; Architecture
    - France Series 6/10 - Men and women walking a in park. 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid543 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Women; Men; Photographic Prints; France; Group Portraits
    - France Series 7/10 - People sitting in chairs at a park with trees. 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid544 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Children; Women; France; Hats; Men; Parks; Facial Hair; Gardens; Group Portraits
    - France Series 8/10 - A tree lined street with large multi story buildings. 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid545 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Streets/Roads; Gelatin Silver Prints; France; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Men; Buildings; Houses
    - France Series 9/10 - A street view with some people walking. 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid546 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Bicycles/Tricycles; Photographic Prints; Women; Men; Architecture; Houses; France; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps
    - France Series 10/10 - A man sitting by a pond in a park. 6.5 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid547 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Individual Portraits; Ponds; France; Photographic Prints; Parks; Lakes; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Nurse Series, 1403
    - Nurse Series - A group of nurses with men. 12.1 x 8.2 cm, Undated; cuid529 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Men; Women; Nurses; Uniforms; Facial Hair
    - Nurse Series - A nurse wearing a head cover holding a basket of potatoes. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 19 August 1952; cuid530 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Women; Photographic Prints; Nurses; Head Covers/Veils; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits
    - Nurse Series - Two nurses with a man. 8.0 x 11.3 cm, Undated; cuid531 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Men; Women; Nurses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Nurse Series - A nurse drinking out of a glass bottle. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, 1951; cuid532 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Individual Portraits; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Nurses; Arabic Writing
    - Nurse Series - A nurse with a friend posing on the beach. 12.8 x 17.9 cm, 22 July 1953; cuid533 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Nurses; Women; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Group Portraits
    - Nurse Series - A nurse in a bathing suit posing on the beach. 12.8 x 17.9 cm, 22 July 1953; cuid534 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Jewelry; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Nurses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Women
    - Nurse Series - A group of nurses in uniform with other people. 8.0 x 12.0 cm, 1952; cuid535 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Children; Men; Women; Uniforms; Nurses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair
    - Nurse Series - A nurse in uniform with three men in galabeyas. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 16 May 1952; cuid536 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Group Portraits; Women; Photographic Prints; Regional/National Dress; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Men; Uniforms; Nurses; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series, 1405
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Two men in three-piece suits and hats, leaning on a car on a street. 8.4 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid628 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Germany; Men; Cars/Trucks; Smoking; Cigarettes; Outdoors; Streets/Roads; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Transportation; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting in the driver's seat of a convertible car, a 1936 Adler Trumpf Junior Cabrio. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid629 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Women; Individual Portraits; Cars/Trucks; Outdoors; Streets/Roads; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Three women and one man standing on the sidewalk in front of a Dodge (car). 6.1 x 8.6 cm, Undated; cuid630 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Photographic Prints; Germany; Women; Men; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Group Portraits; Transportation; Facial Hair
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a light dress seated at an outdoor cafe near a lake. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid631 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Photographic Prints; Women; Jewelry; Gardens; Individual Portraits; Restaurants/bars; Lakes
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A young girl standing on a dirt path with a walking stick wearing winter clothes. 6.2 x 6.0 cm, November 1937; cuid632 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Photographic Prints; Girls; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Individual Portraits; Children; Countryside/Rural; English Writing; Budapest, Hungary
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A young woman wearing a white bathing suit sitting on the beach (same woman as ref662). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid633 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Beaches; Individual Portraits; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Women
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting on the beach in a white bathing suit (same woman as ref661). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid634 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Berlin, Germany; Individual Portraits; Women
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a fur trimmed coat standing in front of a car (same location as ref666). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid635 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Women; Countryside/Rural; Cars/Trucks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fur Garments; Berlin, Germany; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Individual Portraits; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - The 1936 Olympics stadium with Adolf Hitler on the balcony. 6.1 x 8.9cm, August 1936; cuid636 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Fascism; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military/Soldiers; Berlin, Germany; Flags; Olympic Games; Men; Photographic Prints; Stadiums; Women; Sports; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Audiences/Spectators; Hitler, Adolf, 1889-1945
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Two men standing on a balcony (same location as ref669). 8.6 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid637 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Photographic Prints; Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing in front a car (same location as ref663). 9.0 x 5.9 cm, Undated; cuid638 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Men; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Cars/Trucks; Individual Portraits; Transportation; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a patterned swimsuit. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid639 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Individual Portraits; Berlin, Germany; Smoking; Cigarettes; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Street Lamps
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a pencil skirt suit standing in front of a convertible (same location as ref670). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid640 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Cars/Trucks; Individual Portraits; Women; Architecture; Germany; Countryside/Rural; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg (right) with another man on a balcony (same location as 665). 6.0 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid641 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Photographic Prints; Houses; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing with his arms behind his back in front of a convertible (same location as ref668). 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid642 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Flags; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Individual Portraits; Men; Cars/Trucks; Germany; Houses; Photographic Prints; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing in a garden in a robe and bathing suit. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid643 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Berlin, Germany; Gardens; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Individual Portraits; Outdoors
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman standing in a white dress and hat at a race track. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid644 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Hats; Berlin, Germany; Animals; Photographic Prints; Horses; Horse Racing; Stadiums
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and a woman in a dark dress standing in front of a large estate. 6.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid645 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Gardens; Buildings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a fur-trimmed coat standing on a tree-lined road. 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid646 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Fur Garments; Individual Portraits; Berlin, Germany; Hats; Women; Photographic Prints; Countryside/Rural
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting in a convertible car facing the trunk. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid647 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Germany; Photographic Prints; Countryside/Rural; Flags; Women; Buildings; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a brooch and hat, seated at a cafe outdoors. 6.2 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid648 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Women; Photographic Prints; Countryside/Rural; Jewelry; Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Germany; Restaurants/bars
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman at a beach in a white bathing suit putting on her shoe. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid649 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Beaches; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Photographic Prints; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Germany
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A man and a woman standing on the steps in front of Sanssouci Palace, Potsdam. 8.9 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid650 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Photographic Prints; Potsdam, Germany; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Men; Palaces; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg sitting on the beach with his arms crossed. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid651 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Beaches; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Berlin, Germany; Individual Portraits